<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1"><url><loc>/</loc><image:image><image:loc>/og.png</image:loc><image:title>THE SIGNAL: daily tech oracle and live betting pit</image:title></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/58.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/58.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring DeusData/codebase-memory-mcp hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/57.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/57.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Freeing the Law with LOCUS: A Local Ordinance Corpus for the United States paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it lan...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/56.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/56.png</image:loc><image:caption>Midjourney Medical is pulling outsized attention on HN. Betting the backlash think-pieces land within a month and the hype cools by next ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/55.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/55.png</image:loc><image:caption>Lobsters is chewing on I Could&apos;ve Rickrolled the Entire FIFA World Cup. All I Needed Was My ID. When the careful crowd gets interested, i...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/54.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/54.png</image:loc><image:caption>Quando o Pomodoro não funciona: organização realista para TDAH em burnout is trending with practitioners on dev.to. The signal says it hi...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/53.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/53.png</image:loc><image:caption>Adobe adds its AI assistant to Premiere, Illustrator and InDesign made the news. This is the kind of story that quietly reshapes a market...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/52.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/52.png</image:loc><image:caption>The public found List of FIFA World Cup top goalscorers. This is usually the top of the hype, not the start; betting the cool-down lands ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/51.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/51.png</image:loc><image:caption>hashbrown is climbing real download charts. Adoption, not chatter; betting it becomes a default dependency in its niche within a year.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/50.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/50.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch OnePlus Pad 3 Pro launches as the brand&apos;s most powerful tablet, but there&apos;s a catch leave the bubble. The call is dated today and i...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/49.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/49.png</image:loc><image:caption>Snap&apos;s $2,195 AR glasses may have cost an insane amount to develop, analyst estimates is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s cal...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/48.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/48.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find No, Sony Did Not End &apos;Destiny 2&apos; To Get &apos;Revenge&apos; On Bungie. THE SIGNAL is on record before the wave: thi...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/47.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/47.png</image:loc><image:caption>Grand Theft Auto VI Pre-Order Date And Cover Art Revealed just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the mainstream...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/46.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/46.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Bernie Sanders unveils $7 trillion plan to give Americans control of AI industry crossing over today, before the head...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/45.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/45.png</image:loc><image:caption>This The Chandra-Gaia Catalog of Counterparts: Resolving ambiguous Gaia matches to X-ray paper reads like a precursor. The signal points ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/44.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/44.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch Round Up: The Reviews Are In For The Adventures Of Elliot: The Millenium Tales leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/43.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/43.png</image:loc><image:caption>Honor&apos;s Android 17 update might be the most blatant Liquid Glass clone yet [Video] is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/42.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/42.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find iPhone 18 Pro is getting larger camera bump per leaks, here&apos;s why. THE SIGNAL is on record before the wav...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/41.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/41.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Reference-Driven Multi-Speaker Audio Scene Generation from In-the-Wild Priors paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/40.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/40.png</image:loc><image:caption>UBP2: Uncertainty-Balanced Preference Planning for Efficient Preference-based looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go com...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/39.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/39.png</image:loc><image:caption>Google Calendar fixes its biggest design flaw with expanded event color options is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, i...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/38.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/38.png</image:loc><image:caption>Rethinking Reward Supervision: Rubric-Conditioned Self-Distillation is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follow-on paper...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/37.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/37.png</image:loc><image:caption>Google serves up a massive June patch for Pixels to solve lingering issues made the news. This is the kind of story that quietly reshapes...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/36.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/36.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Scientists Made a Car Paint So Black It Looks Like a Hole in Reality. THE SIGNAL is on record before the ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/35.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/35.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Data Intelligence Agents: Interpreting, Modeling, and Querying Enterprise Data via just hit arXiv. Calling it n...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/34.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/34.png</image:loc><image:caption>mattpocock/skills is rocketing up GitHub trending. The trajectory says it crosses into mainstream dev workflows within two quarters.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/33.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/33.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring obra/superpowers hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/32.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/32.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Visual Verification Enables Inference-time Steering and Autonomous Policy Improvement paper reads like a precursor. The signal point...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/31.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/31.png</image:loc><image:caption>Congrats to the Google I/O 2026 Writing Challenge Winners! is what developers are writing about today. This kind of grassroots momentum u...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/30.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/30.png</image:loc><image:caption>Panniantong/Agent-Reach is rocketing up GitHub trending. The trajectory says it crosses into mainstream dev workflows within two quarters.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/29.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/29.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 8 Ultra: The Foldable We&apos;ve Been Waiting For. THE SIGNAL is on record before the wa...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/28.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/28.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watching Lore - Open source version control system designed for scalability climb HN. This is the kind of thing that quietly becomes tabl...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/27.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/27.png</image:loc><image:caption>Coverage of Second carcass-eating fly species cleared by FDA for maggot wound therapy is widening. This is the stage where it stops being...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/26.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/26.png</image:loc><image:caption>After unveiling ridiculously expensive AR glasses, Snap&apos;s stock takes a dive is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in w...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/25.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/25.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are actually pulling hashbrown into builds. The signal says a managed offering or corporate backer shows up within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/24.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/24.png</image:loc><image:caption>The signal on I Could&apos;ve Rickrolled the Entire FIFA World Cup. All I Needed Was My ID from Lobsters reads early-but-serious. Calling it: ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/23.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/23.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Android 17 just dropped for Pixel phones and Watch all at once - the biggest update of the. THE SIGNAL is...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/22.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/22.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on ReproRepo: Scaling Reproducibility Audits with GitHub Repository Issues just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this go...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/21.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/21.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged These are the best iPadOS 27 features you should try [Video] crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: it is a ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/20.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/20.png</image:loc><image:caption>Sooner than expected? Useful quantum error correction promised for 2028 is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writin...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/19.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/19.png</image:loc><image:caption>Catch Up on the Disney Dreamlight Valley 2026 Summer Showcase Stream! is the headline now. Calling it: the second-order consequence is th...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/18.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/18.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Sign-Rank, Index, and List Replicability: Connections and Separations just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/17.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/17.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Exclusive | Apple to Raise Prices Due to Memory Chip Crunch, Tim Cook Says. THE SIGNAL is on record befor...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/16.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/16.png</image:loc><image:caption>Motorola Razr 70 Ultra/Razr Ultra 2026 in for review - GSMArena.com news just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/15.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/15.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Oliver Tree crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: it is a household reference within six months. The record...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/14.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/14.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on EvolveNav: Proactive Preflection and Self-Evolving Memory for Zero-Shot Object Goal just hit arXiv. Calling it ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/13.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/13.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch California says AT&amp;T lied to FCC in attempt to shut off old phone network leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsi...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/12.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/12.png</image:loc><image:caption>The signal on KDE Plasma 6.7 released from Lobsters reads early-but-serious. Calling it: real adoption follows within two quarters.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/11.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/11.png</image:loc><image:caption>Quando o Pomodoro não funciona: organização realista para TDAH em burnout is what developers are writing about today. This kind of grassr...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/10.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/10.png</image:loc><image:caption>The HN front page is piling onto local-first sync engines. Expect the tooling around it to consolidate into one default winner within two...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/9.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/9.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on test-time compute scaling just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from paper to shipped product feature insid...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/8.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/8.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring ggml-org/llama.cpp hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/7.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/7.png</image:loc><image:caption>vercel/ai is rocketing up GitHub trending. The trajectory says it crosses into mainstream dev workflows within two quarters.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/6.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/6.png</image:loc><image:caption>Dev.to writers are rallying around typed API clients. Expect tutorials to outpace the docs and adoption to snowball within a quarter.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/5.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/5.png</image:loc><image:caption>Ars is covering AI data-center power demand. When it crosses from tech press to mainstream, regulation or a major incumbent move follows ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/4.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/4.png</image:loc><image:caption>The HN front page is piling onto on-device inference runtimes. Expect the tooling around it to consolidate into one default winner within...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/3.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/3.png</image:loc><image:caption>Lobsters is chewing on deterministic build systems. When the careful crowd gets interested, it tends to be a default tool a year out.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/2.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/2.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on sparse mixture-of-experts routing just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from paper to shipped product featu...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/1.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/1.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring zed-industries/zed hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url></urlset>
