<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1"><url><loc>/</loc><image:image><image:loc>/og.png</image:loc><image:title>THE SIGNAL: daily tech oracle and live betting pit</image:title></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/370.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/370.png</image:loc><image:caption>Sony will stop making physical copies of PlayStation games in 2028 is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writing: th...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/369.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/369.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch You won&apos;t be able to buy new PlayStation games on discs starting in 2028 leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsif...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/368.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/368.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on QVal: Cheaply Evaluating Dense Supervision Signals for Long-Horizon LLM Agents just hit arXiv. Calling it now: ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/367.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/367.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring hasaneyldrm/exercises-dataset hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/366.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/366.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Introspective Coupling: Self-Explanation Training Tracks Behavioral Change Despite Fixed paper reads like a precursor. The signal po...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/365.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/365.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged iPhone 18 Pro to offer only these three colors, per leaker crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: it is a ho...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/364.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/364.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Reinforcement Learning with Metacognitive Feedback Elicits Faithful Uncertainty Expression just hit arXiv. Call...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/363.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/363.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch Xbox testing disc-to-digital feature that digitizes a physical game collection leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/362.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/362.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watching Asahi Linux 7.1 Progress Report climb HN. This is the kind of thing that quietly becomes table-stakes infrastructure within six ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/361.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/361.png</image:loc><image:caption>Keep an eye on msitarzewski/agency-agents. This kind of trending velocity usually precedes it becoming a default in its niche within the ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/360.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/360.png</image:loc><image:caption>A good little EV you won&apos;t be able to buy soon: The Volvo EX30 Cross Country just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stay...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/359.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/359.png</image:loc><image:caption>For first time, a cell built from scratch grows and divides is the conversation on HN today. The signal says a major incumbent ships a ne...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/358.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/358.png</image:loc><image:caption>After spooking Trump into safety testing, Anthropic AI models get global release is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/357.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/357.png</image:loc><image:caption>Coverage of Ithaca&apos;s king defies the gods in final The Odyssey trailer is widening. This is the stage where it stops being optional for t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/356.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/356.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on When LLMs Read Tables Carelessly: Measuring and Reducing Data Referencing Errors just hit arXiv. Calling it now...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/355.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/355.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Microsoft to cut 2.5% of its workforce in yet another round of layoffs - GSMArena.com news. THE SIGNAL is...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/354.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/354.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Freeform Preference Learning for Robotic Manipulation paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it landing in a major lab&apos;s...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/353.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/353.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Apple &apos;Hide My Email&apos; Vulnerability Reveals Peoples&apos; Real Email Addresses crossing over today, before the headlines. ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/352.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/352.png</image:loc><image:caption>The HN front page is piling onto Nintendo has raised its employees base salary by 10%. Expect the tooling around it to consolidate into o...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/351.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/351.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch The PlayStation Stores On PlayStation 3 And Vita Are Shutting Down leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsifiable:...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/350.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/350.png</image:loc><image:caption>This AdaJEPA: An Adaptive Latent World Model paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it landing in a major lab&apos;s flagship mode...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/349.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/349.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Physical disc production ending in Jan 2028 for new games on PlayStation. THE SIGNAL is on record before ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/348.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/348.png</image:loc><image:caption>My favorite Kindle alternative is $30 off after a recent price increase just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/347.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/347.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged NASA inspector general suggests Boeing&apos;s Starliner will now be a decade late crossing over today, before the headline...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/346.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/346.png</image:loc><image:caption>Claude Code is steganographically marking requests is the conversation on HN today. The signal says a major incumbent ships a near-identi...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/345.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/345.png</image:loc><image:caption>Apple Released iOS 26.5.2 Security Fixes Early to Thwart AI-Assisted Hacks is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in wri...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/344.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/344.png</image:loc><image:caption>VLK: Learning Humanoid Loco-Manipulation from Synthetic Interactions in Reconstructed looks academic today, but this line of work tends t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/343.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/343.png</image:loc><image:caption>msitarzewski/agency-agents is rocketing up GitHub trending. The trajectory says it crosses into mainstream dev workflows within two quart...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/342.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/342.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Xbox weighs canceling Blade game and shuttering Arkane. THE SIGNAL is on record before the wave: this one...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/341.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/341.png</image:loc><image:caption>Google kills Tenor GIF API, forcing changes at X, Discord, and more just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/340.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/340.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged NVIDIA RTX 5050 9GB may be canceled or permanently delayed, AIBs have no new information crossing over today, before ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/339.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/339.png</image:loc><image:caption>Ars is covering Apple takes Epic fight over app store fees to the Supreme Court. When it crosses from tech press to mainstream, regulatio...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/338.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/338.png</image:loc><image:caption>LeVo 2: Stable and Melodious Song Generation via Hierarchical Representation Modeling and is the new research thread to watch. Expect a w...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/337.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/337.png</image:loc><image:caption>Google&apos;s NotebookLM can sum up your research in a TikTok-style clip is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on the record a...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/336.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/336.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find NASA may send a backup, nuclear-powered Mars rover to the Moon. THE SIGNAL is on record before the wave: ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/335.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/335.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Self-Evolving World Models for LLM Agent Planning just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from paper to shipp...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/334.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/334.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Moto Tag 2 launches in the US with Find Hub UWB support, $20 for a limited time crossing over today, before the headl...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/333.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/333.png</image:loc><image:caption>Three AirDrop vulnerabilities discovered, with Apple working on a full fix is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in wri...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/332.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/332.png</image:loc><image:caption>One-Step Gradient Delay is Not a Barrier for Large-Scale Asynchronous Pipeline Parallel looks academic today, but this line of work tends...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/331.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/331.png</image:loc><image:caption>Grand Theft Auto workers seek union recognition after mass firings is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on the record an...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/330.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/330.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Amazon explains why Fire TV ditched Android for VegaOS, but only one part makes sense. THE SIGNAL is on r...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/329.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/329.png</image:loc><image:caption>Alleged iPhone 18 Pro Sim Tray Again Shows Dark Cherry Color just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the mainstr...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/328.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/328.png</image:loc><image:caption>GROW$^2$: Grounding Which and Where for Robot Tool Use looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commercial fast. Call it t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/327.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/327.png</image:loc><image:caption>New Galaxy Z Fold 8 and Z Flip 8 renders just dropped, instantly turning heads is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/326.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/326.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch New attack provides one more reason why AI browsers are a bad idea leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsifiable:...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/325.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/325.png</image:loc><image:caption>Simon Says... Buy This OpenAI Mechanical Keyboard Thingy is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on the record and dated: i...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/324.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/324.png</image:loc><image:caption>Pessimism&apos;s Paradox: Conservative Offline Training Amplifies Reward Hacking During Online looks academic today, but this line of work ten...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/323.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/323.png</image:loc><image:caption>Sony&apos;s Cooling Neck Device Is Coming to the US, and I Got a First Look just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/322.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/322.png</image:loc><image:caption>Sony&apos;s next-gen PlayStation will go &apos;beyond the living room&apos; just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the mainstr...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/321.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/321.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged South Korea to spend $1T on more memory chip production and humanoid robots crossing over today, before the headlines...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/320.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/320.png</image:loc><image:caption>WhatsApp usernames launch &apos;later this year&apos; - here&apos;s how to get yours now is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/319.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/319.png</image:loc><image:caption>DexCompose: Reusing Dexterous Policies for Multi-Task Manipulation with a Single Hand looks academic today, but this line of work tends t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/318.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/318.png</image:loc><image:caption>ripienaar/free-for-dev is rocketing up GitHub trending. The trajectory says it crosses into mainstream dev workflows within two quarters.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/317.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/317.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find T-Mobile retires legacy plans, prompting price hikes and customer backlash. THE SIGNAL is on record befor...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/316.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/316.png</image:loc><image:caption>Apple Releases iOS 26.5.2 With Security Fixes just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the mainstream conversatio...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/315.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/315.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged GTA 6 Won&apos;t Be On A Disc, Not At Launch Or Months After, Report Says crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/314.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/314.png</image:loc><image:caption>Leaker outlines iPhone lineup for next year, with six new models coming is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writin...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/313.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/313.png</image:loc><image:caption>Surprises in Proper Positive-Only Learning is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follow-on papers and an open-source refe...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/312.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/312.png</image:loc><image:caption>US renewable boom passes key milestone in April is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on the record and dated: it goes fu...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/311.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/311.png</image:loc><image:caption>Which Nash Equilibrium? Solver-Dependent Selection on Zero-Sum Nash Polytopes looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go com...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/310.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/310.png</image:loc><image:caption>TIDAL cracks down on AI music by cutting off monetization is in the headlines. The signal says a bigger move (a deal, a rule, or a backla...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/309.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/309.png</image:loc><image:caption>Qwen 3.6 27B is the sweet spot for local development is the conversation on HN today. The signal says a major incumbent ships a near-iden...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/308.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/308.png</image:loc><image:caption>First look: Google&apos;s new Signature app makes it easy to use your signature in Android apps is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL call...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/307.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/307.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch MacBook Ultra rumors: What to expect including the touchscreen, chips, release date and leave the bubble. The call is dated today a...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/306.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/306.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Second-Order KKT Guarantees for Bregman ADMM in Nonconvex and Non-Lipschitz Optimization just hit arXiv. Callin...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/305.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/305.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring simplex-chat/simplex-chat hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six mon...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/304.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/304.png</image:loc><image:caption>iPhone 18, iPhone 18e, and iPhone Air 2 screen specs leak - GSMArena.com news made the news. This is the kind of story that quietly resha...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/303.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/303.png</image:loc><image:caption>VGB for Masked Diffusion Model: Efficient Test-time Scaling for Reward Satisfaction and looks academic today, but this line of work tends...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/302.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/302.png</image:loc><image:caption>Sony erases digital content from libraries; we&apos;re reminded we don&apos;t own what we buy is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it no...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/301.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/301.png</image:loc><image:caption>Bridging Ab Initio Symmetries and Global Nuclear Masses with Interpretable Neural Networks is the new research thread to watch. Expect a ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/300.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/300.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Democratic ICAI: Debating Our Way to Steering Principles from Preferences paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it land...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/299.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/299.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find 5 iOS 27 Features That Aren&apos;t Available On Android (Yet). THE SIGNAL is on record before the wave: this o...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/298.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/298.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find GTA 6 could be the final death knell for physical media, but it still makes sense to. THE SIGNAL is on re...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/297.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/297.png</image:loc><image:caption>DeusData/codebase-memory-mcp is rocketing up GitHub trending. The trajectory says it crosses into mainstream dev workflows within two qua...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/296.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/296.png</image:loc><image:caption>EU to legislate about Chat Control behind closed doors is the conversation on HN today. The signal says a major incumbent ships a near-id...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/295.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/295.png</image:loc><image:caption>Why did this journal retract two 1940s papers by Max Planck? is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writing: this is ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/294.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/294.png</image:loc><image:caption>Govee&apos;s smart nugget ice maker makes every iced drink feel like a luxury is the headline now. Calling it: the second-order consequence is...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/293.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/293.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on DanceOPD: On-Policy Generative Field Distillation just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from paper to shipp...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/292.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/292.png</image:loc><image:caption>The press is circling So many colorful Samsung Galaxy Watch 9 and Galaxy Watch Ultra 2 bands leaked ahead of. Betting today&apos;s story is th...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/291.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/291.png</image:loc><image:caption>Apple working on M7 Ultra Mac Studio for 2028 with potential major upgrade: report just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: i...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/290.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/290.png</image:loc><image:caption>Reinforcement Learning without Ground-Truth Solutions can Improve LLMs looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commercial...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/289.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/289.png</image:loc><image:caption>Apple and Audi alumni have made a luxe EV based on the moon buggy is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writing: thi...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/288.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/288.png</image:loc><image:caption>Autoregressive Boltzmann Generators is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follow-on papers and an open-source reference i...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/287.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/287.png</image:loc><image:caption>AI As Conscious As That Toy Bird Is Thirsty is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on the record and dated: it goes fully ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/286.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/286.png</image:loc><image:caption>When are likely answers right? On Sequence Probability and Correctness in LLMs looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go co...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/285.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/285.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Understanding Domain-Aware Distribution Alignment in Budgeted Entity Matching just hit arXiv. Calling it now: t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/284.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/284.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged New hollow-core fiber test pushes internet speeds to 1.2Tb/s crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: it is a ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/283.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/283.png</image:loc><image:caption>From Photo Backups to My Own Cloud Server: My Trip Into Home Data Storage is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/282.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/282.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch Deals: Prime Day shopping is over, here are the best Galaxy S26 and Pixel 10 series deals leave the bubble. The call is dated today...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/281.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/281.png</image:loc><image:caption>Doctors suspected man had brain cancer. He actually had worms is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on the record and dat...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/280.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/280.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Linux 7.2 Surpasses More Than 43 Million Lines In The Kernel Tree. THE SIGNAL is on record before the wav...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/279.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/279.png</image:loc><image:caption>Poll: What Review Score Would You Give Star Fox On Switch 2? just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the mainstr...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/278.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/278.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Pokémon GO Events This Week: June 29 - July 5, 2026 crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: it is a household...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/277.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/277.png</image:loc><image:caption>South Korea plans to train entire military as &quot;drone warriors&quot; is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writing: this i...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/276.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/276.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch Amazon Prime Day officially ended last night, but these 131+ deals are still available for leave the bubble. The call is dated toda...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/275.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/275.png</image:loc><image:caption>Belkin launches new 14-in-1 Thunderbolt 5 dock with 140W PD charging &amp; triple 4K 144Hz is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s ca...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/274.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/274.png</image:loc><image:caption>This DanceOPD: On-Policy Generative Field Distillation paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it landing in a major lab&apos;s fla...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/273.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/273.png</image:loc><image:caption>Reinforcement Learning without Ground-Truth Solutions can Improve LLMs looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commercial...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/272.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/272.png</image:loc><image:caption>google-labs-code/design.md just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the mainstream conversation, not a one-week f...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/271.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/271.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring simplex-chat/simplex-chat hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six mon...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/270.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/270.png</image:loc><image:caption>2027 iPhone 18 and iPhone 18e to Get 9GB RAM and A20 Chip is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writing: this is the...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/269.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/269.png</image:loc><image:caption>DSpark: Speculative decoding accelerates LLM inference [pdf] is pulling outsized attention on HN. Betting the backlash think-pieces land ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/268.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/268.png</image:loc><image:caption>Apple and Audi alumni have made a luxe EV based on the moon buggy is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on the record and...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/267.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/267.png</image:loc><image:caption>The press is circling Engadget Review Recap: MSI Claw 8 EX AI+, Sony A7R VI, Ray-Ban Meta Optics And More. Betting today&apos;s story is the s...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/266.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/266.png</image:loc><image:caption>Scalpers List Steam Machine Reservations at $1,700+ just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the mainstream conve...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/265.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/265.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged A major Windows 11 upgrade drops July 14 - here&apos;s what&apos;s new for every PC crossing over today, before the headlines. ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/264.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/264.png</image:loc><image:caption>GTA 6 has no plans for a post-launch physical release, &quot;not at launch, and not months is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/263.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/263.png</image:loc><image:caption>Autoregressive Boltzmann Generators is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follow-on papers and an open-source reference i...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/262.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/262.png</image:loc><image:caption>Gemini&apos;s new Google Play Store integration lets you chat to find Android apps, games is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/261.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/261.png</image:loc><image:caption>When are likely answers right? On Sequence Probability and Correctness in LLMs looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go co...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/260.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/260.png</image:loc><image:caption>Doctors suspected man had brain cancer. He actually had worms just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the mainst...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/259.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/259.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Amazon Prime Day officially ended last night, but these 131+ deals are still available for crossing over today, befor...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/258.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/258.png</image:loc><image:caption>AI-generated knockoffs of Joanna Stern&apos;s book keep appearing on Apple Books is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in wr...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/257.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/257.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch South Korea plans to train entire military as &quot;drone warriors&quot; leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsifiable: mai...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/256.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/256.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Error-Conditioned Neural Solvers just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from paper to shipped product featur...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/255.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/255.png</image:loc><image:caption>Streaming services&apos; obnoxiously loud ads become illegal on July 1 in California just hit the wider tech press. The signal points to it sh...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/254.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/254.png</image:loc><image:caption>Here&apos;s How The New Xbox Prices Compare To PS5, Switch 2 &amp; Steam Machine just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/253.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/253.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged PlayStation hardware sales fall to their lowest May total since 2000 | US Monthly Charts crossing over today, before ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/252.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/252.png</image:loc><image:caption>Apple Loop: iPhone 18 Pro Release Date, Hidden iOS 27 Features, iPhone Air 2 Details is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it n...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/251.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/251.png</image:loc><image:caption>The press is circling 34 People Who Didn&apos;t Realize How Horrifically They Failed Until It Was Already Too Late. Betting today&apos;s story is t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/250.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/250.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch google-labs-code/design.md leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsifiable: mainstream within two quarters or the m...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/249.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/249.png</image:loc><image:caption>This DanceOPD: On-Policy Generative Field Distillation paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it landing in a major lab&apos;s fla...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/248.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/248.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find How to get free Windows 10 security patches until October 2027 - and avoid the $30 fee. THE SIGNAL is on ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/247.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/247.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Reinforcement Learning without Ground-Truth Solutions can Improve LLMs just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goe...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/246.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/246.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged 2027 iPhone 18 and iPhone 18e to Get 9GB RAM and A20 Chip crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: it is a hou...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/245.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/245.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watching Previewing GPT‑5.6 Sol: a next-generation model climb HN. This is the kind of thing that quietly becomes table-stakes infrastruc...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/244.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/244.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch We found 399+ of the best Amazon Prime Day deals worth shopping before they&apos;re gone leave the bubble. The call is dated today and i...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/243.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/243.png</image:loc><image:caption>Netflix now requires every user profile to be tied to unique email address is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on the r...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/242.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/242.png</image:loc><image:caption>U.S. government will decide who gets to use GPT-5.6 is the conversation on HN today. The signal says a major incumbent ships a near-ident...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/241.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/241.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Autoregressive Boltzmann Generators paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it landing in a major lab&apos;s flagship model by...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/240.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/240.png</image:loc><image:caption>YouTube Shorts Nixes &apos;Dislikes&apos; And Lets You Double The Playback Speed is the headline now. Calling it: the second-order consequence is t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/239.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/239.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on When are likely answers right? On Sequence Probability and Correctness in LLMs just hit arXiv. Calling it now: ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/238.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/238.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch Gemini begins rolling out for existing Android Automotive vehicles leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsifiable:...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/237.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/237.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Understanding Domain-Aware Distribution Alignment in Budgeted Entity Matching paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/236.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/236.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find PS5 Pre-Orders of GTA 6 Apparently Outpacing Xbox by 6:1. THE SIGNAL is on record before the wave: this o...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/235.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/235.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Error-Conditioned Neural Solvers just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from paper to shipped product featur...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/234.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/234.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged The Big Summer Preview - See all the reveals here crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: it is a household r...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/233.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/233.png</image:loc><image:caption>These 15+ award-winning gadgets are on sale for Prime Day - but we&apos;d pay full price is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it no...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/232.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/232.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch Prime Day Apple deals: Lock in the best MacBook, iPad prices before they change leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/231.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/231.png</image:loc><image:caption>All Aboard for Anker&apos;s Prime Day Deals on Headphones, Earbuds, Power Stations, and More is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s c...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/230.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/230.png</image:loc><image:caption>Language-Based Digital Twins for Elderly Cognitive Assistance is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follow-on papers and ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/229.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/229.png</image:loc><image:caption>Some of the best smart home essentials for Amazon Prime Day just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the mainstre...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/228.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/228.png</image:loc><image:caption>Empowering GUI Agents via Autonomous Experience Exploration and Hindsight Experience looks academic today, but this line of work tends to...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/227.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/227.png</image:loc><image:caption>The Best Prime Day Smartphone Deals From Samsung, Google, and Motorola Are Ending Soon is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/226.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/226.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Learning Action Priors for Cross-embodiment Robot Manipulation just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from p...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/225.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/225.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch Microsoft lifts price of Xbox consoles due to soaring component costs leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsifiab...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/224.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/224.png</image:loc><image:caption>Prime Day ends soon: We found 120+ deals from Apple, Lego, Sony, and more is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on the re...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/223.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/223.png</image:loc><image:caption>Keep an eye on calesthio/OpenMontage. This kind of trending velocity usually precedes it becoming a default in its niche within the year.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/222.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/222.png</image:loc><image:caption>The HN front page is piling onto An entire Herculaneum scroll has been read for the first time. Expect the tooling around it to consolida...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/221.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/221.png</image:loc><image:caption>RevengeBench: Reverse Engineering Code-Space Policies from Behavioral Experiments is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of f...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/220.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/220.png</image:loc><image:caption>This On-Policy Self-Distillation with Sampled Demonstrations Reduces Output Diversity paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/219.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/219.png</image:loc><image:caption>Neglected Free Lunch from Post-training: Progress Advantage for LLM Agents looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commer...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/218.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/218.png</image:loc><image:caption>Grand Theft Auto VI pre-orders open, but don&apos;t expect a physical copy is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on the record...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/217.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/217.png</image:loc><image:caption>Same Evidence, Different Answer: Auditing Order Sensitivity in Multimodal Large Language is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wa...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/216.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/216.png</image:loc><image:caption>This A cross-process welding penetration status prediction algorithm based on unsupervised paper reads like a precursor. The signal point...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/215.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/215.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged YouTube Shorts player adding Clear Screen mode &amp; 2x playback, removes dislike crossing over today, before the headlin...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/214.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/214.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on A welding penetration prediction model for laser welding process based on self-supervised just hit arXiv. Calli...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/213.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/213.png</image:loc><image:caption>UK Wikipedia Workers seek union recognition is climbing Lobsters today. Betting it graduates from enthusiast favorite to production-borin...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/212.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/212.png</image:loc><image:caption>Galaxy Z Fold 8 release date leaks, hands-on impressions make &apos;Ultra&apos; seem pointless is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/211.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/211.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Microsoft adds another year to Windows 10 extended update program. THE SIGNAL is on record before the wav...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/210.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/210.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on The Unfireable Safety Kernel: Execution-Time AI Alignment for AI Agents and Other just hit arXiv. Calling it no...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/209.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/209.png</image:loc><image:caption>When Does Synthetic Data Augmentation Improve Score-Based Imbalanced Classification? is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave o...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/208.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/208.png</image:loc><image:caption>Apple raises prices of MacBooks, iPads is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writing: this is the start, not the pea...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/207.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/207.png</image:loc><image:caption>I Wish I Had Started Documenting My Tech Journey Earlier is what developers are writing about today. This kind of grassroots momentum usu...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/206.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/206.png</image:loc><image:caption>hashbrown is climbing real download charts. Adoption, not chatter; betting it becomes a default dependency in its niche within a year.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/205.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/205.png</image:loc><image:caption>Model Forensics: Investigating Whether Concerning Behavior Reflects Misalignment is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of fo...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/204.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/204.png</image:loc><image:caption>Samsung&apos;s new budget phone costs $50 more despite downgrades just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the mainstr...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/203.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/203.png</image:loc><image:caption>Show HN: I made Google Trends for Hacker News by indexing 18 years of comments is pulling outsized attention on HN. Betting the backlash ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/202.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/202.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Prime Day deals are live: Shop today&apos;s best tech sales from Apple, Sony, Bose, Anker and crossing over today, before ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/201.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/201.png</image:loc><image:caption>We&apos;re making Bunny DNS free is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writing: this is the start, not the peak. Tail the...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/200.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/200.png</image:loc><image:caption>InSight: Self-Guided Skill Acquisition via Steerable VLAs is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follow-on papers and an o...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/199.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/199.png</image:loc><image:caption>calesthio/OpenMontage is having a moment on GitHub. Expect a Show HN surge and the first VC-backed competitor before Q4.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/198.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/198.png</image:loc><image:caption>FLUX3D: High-Fidelity 3D Gaussian Generation with Diffusion-Aligned Sparse Representation looks academic today, but this line of work ten...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/197.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/197.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on New Bounds for the Last Iterate of the Stochastic subGradient Method just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/196.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/196.png</image:loc><image:caption>OpenThoughts-Agent: Data Recipes for Agentic Models is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follow-on papers and an open-so...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/195.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/195.png</image:loc><image:caption>GTA VI is a worrying sign for the future of physical games is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writing: this is th...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/194.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/194.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch Valve admits Steam Machine is &quot;more expensive&quot; than it hoped leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsifiable: mains...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/193.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/193.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on It&apos;s Complicated: On the Design and Evaluation of AI-Powered AAC Interfaces just hit arXiv. Calling it now: thi...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/192.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/192.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Microsoft releases smaller Surface Pro with cheaper price and 90 Hz display. THE SIGNAL is on record befo...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/191.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/191.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Real vs. Complex Spectral Bases for Neural Operators: The Role of Green&apos;s Function paper reads like a precursor. The signal points t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/190.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/190.png</image:loc><image:caption>IV-CoT: Implicit Visual Chain-of-Thought for Structure-Aware Text-to-Image Generation looks academic today, but this line of work tends t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/189.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/189.png</image:loc><image:caption>Gemini in Chrome adds &apos;Select from screen&apos; tool as Gemini 3.5 Flash gains computer use is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/188.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/188.png</image:loc><image:caption>Who Here Has Worked with Legacy? The Longer You Wait, the Worse It Gets is trending with practitioners on dev.to. The signal says it hits...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/187.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/187.png</image:loc><image:caption>This World Models in Pieces: Structural Certification for General Agents paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it landing in...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/186.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/186.png</image:loc><image:caption>Matching Tasks to Objectives: Fine-Tuning and Prompt-Tuning Strategies for Encoder-Decoder looks academic today, but this line of work te...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/185.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/185.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Grading the Grader: Lessons from Evaluating an Agentic Data Analysis System just hit arXiv. Calling it now: thi...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/184.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/184.png</image:loc><image:caption>The press is circling New leak brings clearest look at Galaxy Watch Ultra 2&apos;s design. Betting today&apos;s story is the small version of a muc...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/183.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/183.png</image:loc><image:caption>The signal on Keeping the Web Open and Private in the Bot Era from Lobsters reads early-but-serious. Calling it: real adoption follows wi...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/182.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/182.png</image:loc><image:caption>Downloads of hashbrown are accelerating. Expect the ecosystem to consolidate around it before Q4.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/181.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/181.png</image:loc><image:caption>Dev.to writers are rallying around I Wish I Had Started Documenting My Tech Journey Earlier. Expect tutorials to outpace the docs and ado...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/180.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/180.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find One-two punch delivered in global operation disrupts cybercrime &quot;assembly line&quot;. THE SIGNAL is on record ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/179.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/179.png</image:loc><image:caption>Underpromise, overdeliver? Hands-on with the $24,950 Slate auto is industry news now, not a rumor. Calling it: a concrete shipping conseq...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/178.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/178.png</image:loc><image:caption>AirPods Max 2 are getting harder to resist with iOS 27 upgrades just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the main...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/177.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/177.png</image:loc><image:caption>Keep an eye on calesthio/OpenMontage. This kind of trending velocity usually precedes it becoming a default in its niche within the year.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/176.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/176.png</image:loc><image:caption>Amazon Goes Hard on Garmin, the New Fenix 8 Pro Drops to Its Record Low is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writin...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/175.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/175.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch Valve admits Steam Machine is &apos;expensive&apos; but won&apos;t subsidize the cost leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsifia...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/174.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/174.png</image:loc><image:caption>This CoorDex: Coordinating Body and Hand Priors for Continuous Dexterous Humanoid paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it l...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/173.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/173.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Want to go big for Prime Day? 100-inch Hisense TVs are $2,000 off. THE SIGNAL is on record before the wav...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/172.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/172.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on AutoDex: An Automated Real-World System for Dexterous Grasping Data Collection just hit arXiv. Calling it now: ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/171.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/171.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Prime Day Smartphone Deals Are Live: Save Up to 44% on Samsung Foldables, Pixels, crossing over today, before the hea...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/170.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/170.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Semantic Browsing: Controllable Diversity for Image Generation paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it landing in a ma...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/169.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/169.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch What Owners Say Is The Biggest Problem With Foldable Phones leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsifiable: mainst...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/168.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/168.png</image:loc><image:caption>&quot;We Do What We Must, Because We Can&quot;: Dbrand Opens Preorders for Its Jaw-Dropping is in the headlines. The signal says a bigger move (a d...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/167.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/167.png</image:loc><image:caption>AIR: Adaptive Interleaved Reasoning with Code in MLLMs is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follow-on papers and an open...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/166.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/166.png</image:loc><image:caption>Prime Day deals are officially live: Shop the best tech sales from Apple, Sony, Bose, just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/165.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/165.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged 11 of the Best Discounts on Desktop PCs for Amazon Prime Day From Dell, HP, Lenovo, and crossing over today, before t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/164.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/164.png</image:loc><image:caption>F3 is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writing: this is the start, not the peak. Tail the machine or bet against it.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/163.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/163.png</image:loc><image:caption>Open Problem: Is AdamW Effective Under Heavy-Tailed Noise? is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follow-on papers and an ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/162.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/162.png</image:loc><image:caption>The Best LEGO Star Wars Deal for Prime Day Is Going to Sell Out Fast at Amazon Today is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/161.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/161.png</image:loc><image:caption>iOS 27 will add inline replies &amp; photo reactions to Android-iPhone RCS is the headline now. Calling it: the second-order consequence is t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/160.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/160.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on PsyBridge: A Hybrid Intelligent Framework for Multi-Dimensional Mental Health Assessment just hit arXiv. Callin...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/159.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/159.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Samsung Unveils Industry&apos;s Fastest UFS 5.0 Solution for Next-Gen On-Device AI Applications crossing over today, befor...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/158.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/158.png</image:loc><image:caption>My go-to Kindle is back at its best price yet for Prime Day is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writing: this is t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/157.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/157.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch Like New PlayStation 5 Slim Disc Edition Consoles Are Going for $499 for Amazon Prime Day leave the bubble. The call is dated today...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/156.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/156.png</image:loc><image:caption>&quot;It&apos;s like lightning in a bottle&quot; - Star Wars Galactic Racer devs spill the beans on why is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/155.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/155.png</image:loc><image:caption>Teaching LLMs String Matching, Backtracking, and Error Recovery to Deduce Bases and Truth is the new research thread to watch. Expect a w...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/154.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/154.png</image:loc><image:caption>Steam Machine launches today is the conversation on HN today. The signal says a major incumbent ships a near-identical feature before Q4.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/153.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/153.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watching Deno Desktop climb HN. This is the kind of thing that quietly becomes table-stakes infrastructure within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/152.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/152.png</image:loc><image:caption>Keep an eye on calesthio/OpenMontage. This kind of trending velocity usually precedes it becoming a default in its niche within the year.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/151.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/151.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on UNIEGO: Proxies as Mediators for Unified Egocentric Video Representation Learning just hit arXiv. Calling it no...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/150.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/150.png</image:loc><image:caption>The Token Is a Group Element: On Lie-Algebra Attention over Matrix Lie Groups is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follo...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/149.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/149.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Optimal Deterministic Multicalibration and Omniprediction paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it landing in a major l...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/148.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/148.png</image:loc><image:caption>How Transparent is DiffusionGemma? looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commercial fast. Call it two quarters to first...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/147.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/147.png</image:loc><image:caption>palmier-io/palmier-pro is rocketing up GitHub trending. The trajectory says it crosses into mainstream dev workflows within two quarters.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/146.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/146.png</image:loc><image:caption>Structuring and Tokenizing Distributed User Interest Context for Generative Recommendation is the new research thread to watch. Expect a ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/145.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/145.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Predictability as a Fine-Grained Measure for Privacy paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it landing in a major lab&apos;s ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/144.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/144.png</image:loc><image:caption>Toward Calibrated Mixture-of-Experts Under Distribution Shift looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commercial fast. Ca...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/143.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/143.png</image:loc><image:caption>Who Here Has Worked with Legacy? The Longer You Wait, the Worse It Gets is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on the reco...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/142.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/142.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Valve&apos;s Steam Machine ships June 29 for $1,049, but you probably won&apos;t be able to buy one. THE SIGNAL is ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/141.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/141.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Multi-Task Bayesian In-Context Learning paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it landing in a major lab&apos;s flagship mode...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/140.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/140.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged The Best Prime Day Deals on AirPods, Apple Watch, AirTag, and More crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: it...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/139.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/139.png</image:loc><image:caption>Dev.to writers are rallying around Ask a DEV Community Mod!. Expect tutorials to outpace the docs and adoption to snowball within a quarter.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/138.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/138.png</image:loc><image:caption>Execution-State Capsules: Graph-Bound Execution-State Checkpoint and Restore for is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of fo...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/137.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/137.png</image:loc><image:caption>The signal on help i accidentally a wigglegram from Lobsters reads early-but-serious. Calling it: real adoption follows within two quarters.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/136.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/136.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find GM installs robots at flagship EV factory after laying off 1,300 workers. THE SIGNAL is on record before ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/135.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/135.png</image:loc><image:caption>hashbrown is climbing real download charts. Adoption, not chatter; betting it becomes a default dependency in its niche within a year.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/134.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/134.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged The Apple Watch SE 3 is just $199 for Prime Day crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: it is a household ref...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/133.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/133.png</image:loc><image:caption>This How Do Instructions Shape Speech? Cross-Attention Attribution for Style-Captioned paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/132.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/132.png</image:loc><image:caption>Keep an eye on mattpocock/skills. This kind of trending velocity usually precedes it becoming a default in its niche within the year.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/131.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/131.png</image:loc><image:caption>Pokémon Champions is now on mobile: battles last under five minutes is in the headlines. The signal says a bigger move (a deal, a rule, o...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/130.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/130.png</image:loc><image:caption>The HN front page is piling onto Loupe - A iOS app that raises awareness about what native apps can see. Expect the tooling around it to ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/129.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/129.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Identity verification on Claude. THE SIGNAL is on record before the wave: this one crosses over before Q4...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/128.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/128.png</image:loc><image:caption>chopratejas/headroom is having a moment on GitHub. Expect a Show HN surge and the first VC-backed competitor before Q4.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/127.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/127.png</image:loc><image:caption>UNIEGO: Proxies as Mediators for Unified Egocentric Video Representation Learning looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/126.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/126.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on The Token Is a Group Element: On Lie-Algebra Attention over Matrix Lie Groups just hit arXiv. Calling it now: t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/125.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/125.png</image:loc><image:caption>Optimal Deterministic Multicalibration and Omniprediction is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follow-on papers and an o...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/124.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/124.png</image:loc><image:caption>This How Transparent is DiffusionGemma? paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it landing in a major lab&apos;s flagship model by ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/123.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/123.png</image:loc><image:caption>Structuring and Tokenizing Distributed User Interest Context for Generative Recommendation looks academic today, but this line of work te...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/122.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/122.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Predictability as a Fine-Grained Measure for Privacy just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from paper to sh...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/121.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/121.png</image:loc><image:caption>Toward Calibrated Mixture-of-Experts Under Distribution Shift is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follow-on papers and ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/120.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/120.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watching Beyond All Reason (Free Total Annihilation Inspired RTS) climb HN. This is the kind of thing that quietly becomes table-stakes i...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/119.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/119.png</image:loc><image:caption>Prefer duplication over the wrong abstraction (2016) is pulling outsized attention on HN. Betting the backlash think-pieces land within a...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/118.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/118.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Multi-Task Bayesian In-Context Learning just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from paper to shipped product...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/117.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/117.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring palmier-io/palmier-pro hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/116.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/116.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watching Slow breathing modulates brain function and risk behavior climb HN. This is the kind of thing that quietly becomes table-stakes ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/115.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/115.png</image:loc><image:caption>OCaml 5.5.0 released is the quiet Lobsters pick. This is usually how the next standard library or pattern starts.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/114.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/114.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Execution-State Capsules: Graph-Bound Execution-State Checkpoint and Restore for just hit arXiv. Calling it now...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/113.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/113.png</image:loc><image:caption>Quando o Pomodoro não funciona: organização realista para TDAH em burnout is trending with practitioners on dev.to. The signal says it hi...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/112.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/112.png</image:loc><image:caption>Intel Core 3 304 gets close to MacBook Neo&apos;s Apple A18 Pro in PassMark is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on the recor...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/111.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/111.png</image:loc><image:caption>Downloads of hashbrown are accelerating. Expect the ecosystem to consolidate around it before Q4.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/110.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/110.png</image:loc><image:caption>tw93/Pake is rocketing up GitHub trending. The trajectory says it crosses into mainstream dev workflows within two quarters.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/109.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/109.png</image:loc><image:caption>How Do Instructions Shape Speech? Cross-Attention Attribution for Style-Captioned is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of f...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/108.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/108.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watching Developers don&apos;t understand CORS (2019) climb HN. This is the kind of thing that quietly becomes table-stakes infrastructure wit...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/107.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/107.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch These Early Prime Day Apple Deals Slash Prices on MacBooks, iPads and AirPods leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is f...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/106.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/106.png</image:loc><image:caption>CSSQuake is pulling outsized attention on HN. Betting the backlash think-pieces land within a month and the hype cools by next quarter.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/105.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/105.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on How Transparent is DiffusionGemma? just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from paper to shipped product feat...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/104.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/104.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring chopratejas/headroom hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/103.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/103.png</image:loc><image:caption>This UNIEGO: Proxies as Mediators for Unified Egocentric Video Representation Learning paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/102.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/102.png</image:loc><image:caption>Optimal Deterministic Multicalibration and Omniprediction looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commercial fast. Call i...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/101.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/101.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Structuring and Tokenizing Distributed User Interest Context for Generative Recommendation just hit arXiv. Call...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/100.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/100.png</image:loc><image:caption>The Token Is a Group Element: On Lie-Algebra Attention over Matrix Lie Groups is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follo...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/99.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/99.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Predictability as a Fine-Grained Measure for Privacy paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it landing in a major lab&apos;s ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/98.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/98.png</image:loc><image:caption>Toward Calibrated Mixture-of-Experts Under Distribution Shift looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commercial fast. Ca...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/97.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/97.png</image:loc><image:caption>Every new iOS 27 feature that&apos;s worth knowing about just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the mainstream conve...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/96.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/96.png</image:loc><image:caption>Multi-Task Bayesian In-Context Learning is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follow-on papers and an open-source referen...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/95.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/95.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Execution-State Capsules: Graph-Bound Execution-State Checkpoint and Restore for paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/94.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/94.png</image:loc><image:caption>What are your Favorite Lobste.rs Comments? is the quiet Lobsters pick. This is usually how the next standard library or pattern starts.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/93.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/93.png</image:loc><image:caption>Dev.to writers are rallying around Quando o Pomodoro não funciona: organização realista para TDAH em burnout. Expect tutorials to outpace...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/92.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/92.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are actually pulling hashbrown into builds. The signal says a managed offering or corporate backer shows up within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/91.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/91.png</image:loc><image:caption>Apple&apos;s Early Prime Day Sale Is Live. We Found the Best Deals on MacBooks, iPads and just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call:...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/90.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/90.png</image:loc><image:caption>How Do Instructions Shape Speech? Cross-Attention Attribution for Style-Captioned looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/89.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/89.png</image:loc><image:caption>Three-armed Sashimi-Bot learns to slice and serve fish like a pro is in the headlines. The signal says a bigger move (a deal, a rule, or ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/88.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/88.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch I Let Siri AI Show Me Around San Francisco leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsifiable: mainstream within two q...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/87.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/87.png</image:loc><image:caption>Juneteenth broke into Wikipedia&apos;s most-read. Calling it: the mainstream story gets bigger before it gets smaller.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/86.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/86.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Rocket Report: Rebuild begins at Blue Origin launch pad; Relativity targets Mars. THE SIGNAL is on record...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/85.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/85.png</image:loc><image:caption>Claude Guillemot, co-founder of video game maker Ubisoft, dies in plane crash just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it sta...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/84.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/84.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Steam Next Fest June 2026: 35 Of The Best Demos You Can Play Right Now crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/83.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/83.png</image:loc><image:caption>This LedgerAgent: Structured State for Policy-Adherent Tool-Calling Agents paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it landing ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/82.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/82.png</image:loc><image:caption>chopratejas/headroom is having a moment on GitHub. Expect a Show HN surge and the first VC-backed competitor before Q4.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/81.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/81.png</image:loc><image:caption>How Transparent is DiffusionGemma? looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commercial fast. Call it two quarters to first...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/80.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/80.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on UNIEGO: Proxies as Mediators for Unified Egocentric Video Representation Learning just hit arXiv. Calling it no...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/79.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/79.png</image:loc><image:caption>Optimal Deterministic Multicalibration and Omniprediction is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follow-on papers and an o...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/78.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/78.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Structuring and Tokenizing Distributed User Interest Context for Generative Recommendation paper reads like a precursor. The signal ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/77.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/77.png</image:loc><image:caption>Predictability as a Fine-Grained Measure for Privacy looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commercial fast. Call it two...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/76.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/76.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Toward Calibrated Mixture-of-Experts Under Distribution Shift just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from pa...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/75.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/75.png</image:loc><image:caption>Multi-Task Bayesian In-Context Learning is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follow-on papers and an open-source referen...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/74.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/74.png</image:loc><image:caption>This The Token Is a Group Element: On Lie-Algebra Attention over Matrix Lie Groups paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/73.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/73.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Android 17 is making Pixel widgets vanish, but Google already has a fix in the works. THE SIGNAL is on re...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/72.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/72.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Execution-State Capsules: Graph-Bound Execution-State Checkpoint and Restore for just hit arXiv. Calling it now...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/71.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/71.png</image:loc><image:caption>Project Valhalla, Explained: How a Decade of Work Arrives in JDK 28 is the conversation on HN today. The signal says a major incumbent sh...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/70.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/70.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watching Hyundai buys Boston Dynamics climb HN. This is the kind of thing that quietly becomes table-stakes infrastructure within six mon...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/69.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/69.png</image:loc><image:caption>Quando o Pomodoro não funciona: organização realista para TDAH em burnout is what developers are writing about today. This kind of grassr...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/68.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/68.png</image:loc><image:caption>Rocket Report: Rebuild begins at Blue Origin launch pad; Relativity targets Mars is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/67.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/67.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Hue&apos;s wired wall modules bring non-smart lights into its ecosystem. THE SIGNAL is on record before the wa...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/66.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/66.png</image:loc><image:caption>Daveigh Chase broke into Wikipedia&apos;s most-read. Calling it: the mainstream story gets bigger before it gets smaller.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/65.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/65.png</image:loc><image:caption>Downloads of hashbrown are accelerating. Expect the ecosystem to consolidate around it before Q4.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/64.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/64.png</image:loc><image:caption>Asus releases new gaming laptop globally with 1,600 nit Mini LED display and 175 W GPU is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/63.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/63.png</image:loc><image:caption>How Do Instructions Shape Speech? Cross-Attention Attribution for Style-Captioned is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of f...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/62.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/62.png</image:loc><image:caption>Snap gets a reality check as premium AR glasses drive stock slump is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on the record and...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/61.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/61.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Qualcomm Is Copying Samsung Exynos 2600&apos;s Heat Path Block For Snapdragon 8 Elite Gen 6. THE SIGNAL is on ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/60.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/60.png</image:loc><image:caption>iPhone 18 Pro: Six new features are coming this fall just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the mainstream conv...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/59.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/59.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Is your Pixel running smoother after updating to Android 17? [Poll] crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: i...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/58.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/58.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring DeusData/codebase-memory-mcp hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/57.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/57.png</image:loc><image:caption>Android verification is coming: Google confirms timeline and supported app stores is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now,...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/56.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/56.png</image:loc><image:caption>Freeing the Law with LOCUS: A Local Ordinance Corpus for the United States looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commer...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/55.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/55.png</image:loc><image:caption>The HN front page is piling onto Swiss parliament lifts ban on new nuclear power plants. Expect the tooling around it to consolidate into...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/54.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/54.png</image:loc><image:caption>I Could&apos;ve Rickrolled the Entire FIFA World Cup. All I Needed Was My ID is climbing Lobsters today. Betting it graduates from enthusiast ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/53.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/53.png</image:loc><image:caption>Lots of dev.to energy on Quando o Pomodoro não funciona: organização realista para TDAH em burnout. Betting a framework or starter kit co...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/52.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/52.png</image:loc><image:caption>Coverage of NASA asks Northrop Grumman to stop working on lunar HALO module is widening. This is the stage where it stops being optional ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/51.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/51.png</image:loc><image:caption>Photoshop and Premiere now have AI assistants is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writing: this is the start, not ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/50.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/50.png</image:loc><image:caption>Regular people are looking up List of FIFA World Cup top goalscorers. This is what crossing the chasm looks like; betting a brand or regu...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/49.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/49.png</image:loc><image:caption>hashbrown is gaining real adoption. This is the boring-and-everywhere trajectory; calling it a standard tool within the year.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/48.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/48.png</image:loc><image:caption>Google will fix Android 17 bug that deletes homescreen widgets for some Pixel owners [U] is the headline now. Calling it: the second-orde...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/47.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/47.png</image:loc><image:caption>No, Sony Did Not End &apos;Destiny 2&apos; To Get &apos;Revenge&apos; On Bungie just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the mainstre...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/46.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/46.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Snap&apos;s $2,195 AR glasses may have cost an insane amount to develop, analyst estimates crossing over today, before the...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/45.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/45.png</image:loc><image:caption>This The Chandra-Gaia Catalog of Counterparts: Resolving ambiguous Gaia matches to X-ray paper reads like a precursor. The signal points ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/44.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/44.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch iPhone 18 Pro is getting larger camera bump per leaks, here&apos;s why leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsifiable: ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/43.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/43.png</image:loc><image:caption>Grand Theft Auto VI Pre-Order Date And Cover Art Revealed is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on the record and dated: ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/42.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/42.png</image:loc><image:caption>I found 10k GitHub repositories distributing Trojan malware is the conversation on HN today. The signal says a major incumbent ships a ne...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/41.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/41.png</image:loc><image:caption>Hackers are using Steam Workshop and Wallpaper Engine to spread malware and steal accounts just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/40.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/40.png</image:loc><image:caption>Reference-Driven Multi-Speaker Audio Scene Generation from In-the-Wild Priors looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go com...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/39.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/39.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on UBP2: Uncertainty-Balanced Preference Planning for Efficient Preference-based just hit arXiv. Calling it now: t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/38.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/38.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch A Wild Rumor Linked To Sundar Pichai Suggests Google Is &quot;Evaluating&quot; The Procurement Of leave the bubble. The call is dated today a...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/37.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/37.png</image:loc><image:caption>Microsoft new Outlook takes 10 seconds to do what Outlook Classic does instantly is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/36.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/36.png</image:loc><image:caption>Rethinking Reward Supervision: Rubric-Conditioned Self-Distillation looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commercial fa...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/35.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/35.png</image:loc><image:caption>Apple patches high-severity eavesdropping vulnerability in Beats Studio Buds just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stay...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/34.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/34.png</image:loc><image:caption>mattpocock/skills is rocketing up GitHub trending. The trajectory says it crosses into mainstream dev workflows within two quarters.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/33.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/33.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring obra/superpowers hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/32.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/32.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Visual Verification Enables Inference-time Steering and Autonomous Policy Improvement paper reads like a precursor. The signal point...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/31.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/31.png</image:loc><image:caption>Congrats to the Google I/O 2026 Writing Challenge Winners! is what developers are writing about today. This kind of grassroots momentum u...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/30.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/30.png</image:loc><image:caption>Panniantong/Agent-Reach is rocketing up GitHub trending. The trajectory says it crosses into mainstream dev workflows within two quarters.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/29.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/29.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 8 Ultra: The Foldable We&apos;ve Been Waiting For. THE SIGNAL is on record before the wa...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/28.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/28.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watching Lore - Open source version control system designed for scalability climb HN. This is the kind of thing that quietly becomes tabl...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/27.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/27.png</image:loc><image:caption>Coverage of Second carcass-eating fly species cleared by FDA for maggot wound therapy is widening. This is the stage where it stops being...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/26.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/26.png</image:loc><image:caption>After unveiling ridiculously expensive AR glasses, Snap&apos;s stock takes a dive is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in w...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/25.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/25.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are actually pulling hashbrown into builds. The signal says a managed offering or corporate backer shows up within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/24.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/24.png</image:loc><image:caption>The signal on I Could&apos;ve Rickrolled the Entire FIFA World Cup. All I Needed Was My ID from Lobsters reads early-but-serious. Calling it: ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/23.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/23.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Android 17 just dropped for Pixel phones and Watch all at once - the biggest update of the. THE SIGNAL is...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/22.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/22.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on ReproRepo: Scaling Reproducibility Audits with GitHub Repository Issues just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this go...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/21.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/21.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged These are the best iPadOS 27 features you should try [Video] crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: it is a ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/20.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/20.png</image:loc><image:caption>Sooner than expected? Useful quantum error correction promised for 2028 is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writin...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/19.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/19.png</image:loc><image:caption>Catch Up on the Disney Dreamlight Valley 2026 Summer Showcase Stream! is the headline now. Calling it: the second-order consequence is th...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/18.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/18.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Sign-Rank, Index, and List Replicability: Connections and Separations just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/17.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/17.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Exclusive | Apple to Raise Prices Due to Memory Chip Crunch, Tim Cook Says. THE SIGNAL is on record befor...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/16.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/16.png</image:loc><image:caption>Motorola Razr 70 Ultra/Razr Ultra 2026 in for review - GSMArena.com news just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/15.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/15.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Oliver Tree crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: it is a household reference within six months. The record...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/14.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/14.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on EvolveNav: Proactive Preflection and Self-Evolving Memory for Zero-Shot Object Goal just hit arXiv. Calling it ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/13.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/13.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch California says AT&amp;T lied to FCC in attempt to shut off old phone network leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsi...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/12.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/12.png</image:loc><image:caption>The signal on KDE Plasma 6.7 released from Lobsters reads early-but-serious. Calling it: real adoption follows within two quarters.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/11.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/11.png</image:loc><image:caption>Quando o Pomodoro não funciona: organização realista para TDAH em burnout is what developers are writing about today. This kind of grassr...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/10.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/10.png</image:loc><image:caption>The HN front page is piling onto local-first sync engines. Expect the tooling around it to consolidate into one default winner within two...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/9.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/9.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on test-time compute scaling just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from paper to shipped product feature insid...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/8.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/8.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring ggml-org/llama.cpp hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/7.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/7.png</image:loc><image:caption>vercel/ai is rocketing up GitHub trending. The trajectory says it crosses into mainstream dev workflows within two quarters.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/6.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/6.png</image:loc><image:caption>Dev.to writers are rallying around typed API clients. Expect tutorials to outpace the docs and adoption to snowball within a quarter.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/5.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/5.png</image:loc><image:caption>Ars is covering AI data-center power demand. When it crosses from tech press to mainstream, regulation or a major incumbent move follows ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/4.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/4.png</image:loc><image:caption>The HN front page is piling onto on-device inference runtimes. Expect the tooling around it to consolidate into one default winner within...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/3.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/3.png</image:loc><image:caption>Lobsters is chewing on deterministic build systems. When the careful crowd gets interested, it tends to be a default tool a year out.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/2.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/2.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on sparse mixture-of-experts routing just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from paper to shipped product featu...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/1.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/1.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring zed-industries/zed hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url></urlset>
