<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1"><url><loc>/</loc><image:image><image:loc>/og.png</image:loc><image:title>THE SIGNAL: daily tech oracle and live betting pit</image:title></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/106.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/106.png</image:loc><image:caption>There are no instances in ATProto is pulling outsized attention on HN. Betting the backlash think-pieces land within a month and the hype...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/105.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/105.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on How Transparent is DiffusionGemma? just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from paper to shipped product feat...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/104.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/104.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring chopratejas/headroom hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/103.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/103.png</image:loc><image:caption>This UNIEGO: Proxies as Mediators for Unified Egocentric Video Representation Learning paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/102.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/102.png</image:loc><image:caption>Optimal Deterministic Multicalibration and Omniprediction looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commercial fast. Call i...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/101.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/101.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Structuring and Tokenizing Distributed User Interest Context for Generative Recommendation just hit arXiv. Call...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/100.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/100.png</image:loc><image:caption>The Token Is a Group Element: On Lie-Algebra Attention over Matrix Lie Groups is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follo...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/99.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/99.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watching GPT-5.5 hallucinates 3x more than MIT-licensed GLM-5.2 climb HN. This is the kind of thing that quietly becomes table-stakes inf...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/98.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/98.png</image:loc><image:caption>Predictability as a Fine-Grained Measure for Privacy looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commercial fast. Call it two...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/97.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/97.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Toward Calibrated Mixture-of-Experts Under Distribution Shift just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from pa...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/96.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/96.png</image:loc><image:caption>The press is circling A founder of Assassin&apos;s Creed maker Ubisoft killed in a plane crash in western France -. Betting today&apos;s story is t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/95.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/95.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Multi-Task Bayesian In-Context Learning paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it landing in a major lab&apos;s flagship mode...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/94.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/94.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch Every new iOS 27 feature that&apos;s worth knowing about leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsifiable: mainstream wit...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/93.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/93.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Execution-State Capsules: Graph-Bound Execution-State Checkpoint and Restore for just hit arXiv. Calling it now...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/92.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/92.png</image:loc><image:caption>CSSQuake is the conversation on HN today. The signal says a major incumbent ships a near-identical feature before Q4.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/91.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/91.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watching Where to Find the Colors Your Screen Can&apos;t Show You climb HN. This is the kind of thing that quietly becomes table-stakes infras...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/90.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/90.png</image:loc><image:caption>What are your Favorite Lobste.rs Comments? is the quiet Lobsters pick. This is usually how the next standard library or pattern starts.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/89.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/89.png</image:loc><image:caption>Dev.to writers are rallying around Quando o Pomodoro não funciona: organização realista para TDAH em burnout. Expect tutorials to outpace...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/88.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/88.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are actually pulling hashbrown into builds. The signal says a managed offering or corporate backer shows up within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/87.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/87.png</image:loc><image:caption>This How Do Instructions Shape Speech? Cross-Attention Attribution for Style-Captioned paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/86.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/86.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Apple&apos;s Early Prime Day Sale Is Live. We Found the Best Deals on MacBooks, iPads and. THE SIGNAL is on re...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/85.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/85.png</image:loc><image:caption>No Connection: Android 17 messes with 5G on Pixel phones just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the mainstream ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/84.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/84.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Apple Unveiled These Five New Apps Last Week crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: it is a household refere...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/83.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/83.png</image:loc><image:caption>Juneteenth broke into Wikipedia&apos;s most-read. Calling it: the mainstream story gets bigger before it gets smaller.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/82.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/82.png</image:loc><image:caption>chopratejas/headroom is having a moment on GitHub. Expect a Show HN surge and the first VC-backed competitor before Q4.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/81.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/81.png</image:loc><image:caption>How Transparent is DiffusionGemma? looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commercial fast. Call it two quarters to first...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/80.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/80.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on UNIEGO: Proxies as Mediators for Unified Egocentric Video Representation Learning just hit arXiv. Calling it no...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/79.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/79.png</image:loc><image:caption>Optimal Deterministic Multicalibration and Omniprediction is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follow-on papers and an o...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/78.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/78.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Structuring and Tokenizing Distributed User Interest Context for Generative Recommendation paper reads like a precursor. The signal ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/77.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/77.png</image:loc><image:caption>Predictability as a Fine-Grained Measure for Privacy looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commercial fast. Call it two...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/76.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/76.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Toward Calibrated Mixture-of-Experts Under Distribution Shift just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from pa...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/75.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/75.png</image:loc><image:caption>Multi-Task Bayesian In-Context Learning is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of follow-on papers and an open-source referen...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/74.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/74.png</image:loc><image:caption>This The Token Is a Group Element: On Lie-Algebra Attention over Matrix Lie Groups paper reads like a precursor. The signal points to it ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/73.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/73.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Android 17 is making Pixel widgets vanish, but Google already has a fix in the works. THE SIGNAL is on re...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/72.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/72.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Execution-State Capsules: Graph-Bound Execution-State Checkpoint and Restore for just hit arXiv. Calling it now...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/71.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/71.png</image:loc><image:caption>Project Valhalla, Explained: How a Decade of Work Arrives in JDK 28 is the conversation on HN today. The signal says a major incumbent sh...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/70.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/70.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watching Hyundai buys Boston Dynamics climb HN. This is the kind of thing that quietly becomes table-stakes infrastructure within six mon...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/69.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/69.png</image:loc><image:caption>Quando o Pomodoro não funciona: organização realista para TDAH em burnout is what developers are writing about today. This kind of grassr...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/68.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/68.png</image:loc><image:caption>Rocket Report: Rebuild begins at Blue Origin launch pad; Relativity targets Mars is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/67.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/67.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Hue&apos;s wired wall modules bring non-smart lights into its ecosystem. THE SIGNAL is on record before the wa...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/66.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/66.png</image:loc><image:caption>Daveigh Chase broke into Wikipedia&apos;s most-read. Calling it: the mainstream story gets bigger before it gets smaller.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/65.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/65.png</image:loc><image:caption>Downloads of hashbrown are accelerating. Expect the ecosystem to consolidate around it before Q4.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/64.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/64.png</image:loc><image:caption>Asus releases new gaming laptop globally with 1,600 nit Mini LED display and 175 W GPU is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/63.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/63.png</image:loc><image:caption>How Do Instructions Shape Speech? Cross-Attention Attribution for Style-Captioned is the new research thread to watch. Expect a wave of f...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/62.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/62.png</image:loc><image:caption>Snap gets a reality check as premium AR glasses drive stock slump is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on the record and...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/61.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/61.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Qualcomm Is Copying Samsung Exynos 2600&apos;s Heat Path Block For Snapdragon 8 Elite Gen 6. THE SIGNAL is on ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/60.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/60.png</image:loc><image:caption>iPhone 18 Pro: Six new features are coming this fall just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the mainstream conv...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/59.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/59.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Is your Pixel running smoother after updating to Android 17? [Poll] crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: i...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/58.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/58.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring DeusData/codebase-memory-mcp hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/57.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/57.png</image:loc><image:caption>Android verification is coming: Google confirms timeline and supported app stores is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now,...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/56.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/56.png</image:loc><image:caption>Freeing the Law with LOCUS: A Local Ordinance Corpus for the United States looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commer...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/55.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/55.png</image:loc><image:caption>The HN front page is piling onto Swiss parliament lifts ban on new nuclear power plants. Expect the tooling around it to consolidate into...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/54.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/54.png</image:loc><image:caption>I Could&apos;ve Rickrolled the Entire FIFA World Cup. All I Needed Was My ID is climbing Lobsters today. Betting it graduates from enthusiast ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/53.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/53.png</image:loc><image:caption>Lots of dev.to energy on Quando o Pomodoro não funciona: organização realista para TDAH em burnout. Betting a framework or starter kit co...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/52.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/52.png</image:loc><image:caption>Coverage of NASA asks Northrop Grumman to stop working on lunar HALO module is widening. This is the stage where it stops being optional ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/51.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/51.png</image:loc><image:caption>Photoshop and Premiere now have AI assistants is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writing: this is the start, not ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/50.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/50.png</image:loc><image:caption>Regular people are looking up List of FIFA World Cup top goalscorers. This is what crossing the chasm looks like; betting a brand or regu...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/49.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/49.png</image:loc><image:caption>hashbrown is gaining real adoption. This is the boring-and-everywhere trajectory; calling it a standard tool within the year.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/48.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/48.png</image:loc><image:caption>Google will fix Android 17 bug that deletes homescreen widgets for some Pixel owners [U] is the headline now. Calling it: the second-orde...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/47.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/47.png</image:loc><image:caption>No, Sony Did Not End &apos;Destiny 2&apos; To Get &apos;Revenge&apos; On Bungie just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in the mainstre...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/46.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/46.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Snap&apos;s $2,195 AR glasses may have cost an insane amount to develop, analyst estimates crossing over today, before the...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/45.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/45.png</image:loc><image:caption>This The Chandra-Gaia Catalog of Counterparts: Resolving ambiguous Gaia matches to X-ray paper reads like a precursor. The signal points ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/44.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/44.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch iPhone 18 Pro is getting larger camera bump per leaks, here&apos;s why leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsifiable: ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/43.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/43.png</image:loc><image:caption>Grand Theft Auto VI Pre-Order Date And Cover Art Revealed is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on the record and dated: ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/42.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/42.png</image:loc><image:caption>I found 10k GitHub repositories distributing Trojan malware is the conversation on HN today. The signal says a major incumbent ships a ne...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/41.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/41.png</image:loc><image:caption>Hackers are using Steam Workshop and Wallpaper Engine to spread malware and steal accounts just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/40.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/40.png</image:loc><image:caption>Reference-Driven Multi-Speaker Audio Scene Generation from In-the-Wild Priors looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go com...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/39.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/39.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on UBP2: Uncertainty-Balanced Preference Planning for Efficient Preference-based just hit arXiv. Calling it now: t...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/38.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/38.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch A Wild Rumor Linked To Sundar Pichai Suggests Google Is &quot;Evaluating&quot; The Procurement Of leave the bubble. The call is dated today a...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/37.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/37.png</image:loc><image:caption>Microsoft new Outlook takes 10 seconds to do what Outlook Classic does instantly is leaking out of the dev bubble. The machine&apos;s call, on...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/36.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/36.png</image:loc><image:caption>Rethinking Reward Supervision: Rubric-Conditioned Self-Distillation looks academic today, but this line of work tends to go commercial fa...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/35.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/35.png</image:loc><image:caption>Apple patches high-severity eavesdropping vulnerability in Beats Studio Buds just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stay...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/34.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/34.png</image:loc><image:caption>mattpocock/skills is rocketing up GitHub trending. The trajectory says it crosses into mainstream dev workflows within two quarters.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/33.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/33.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring obra/superpowers hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/32.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/32.png</image:loc><image:caption>This Visual Verification Enables Inference-time Steering and Autonomous Policy Improvement paper reads like a precursor. The signal point...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/31.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/31.png</image:loc><image:caption>Congrats to the Google I/O 2026 Writing Challenge Winners! is what developers are writing about today. This kind of grassroots momentum u...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/30.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/30.png</image:loc><image:caption>Panniantong/Agent-Reach is rocketing up GitHub trending. The trajectory says it crosses into mainstream dev workflows within two quarters.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/29.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/29.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 8 Ultra: The Foldable We&apos;ve Been Waiting For. THE SIGNAL is on record before the wa...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/28.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/28.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watching Lore - Open source version control system designed for scalability climb HN. This is the kind of thing that quietly becomes tabl...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/27.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/27.png</image:loc><image:caption>Coverage of Second carcass-eating fly species cleared by FDA for maggot wound therapy is widening. This is the stage where it stops being...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/26.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/26.png</image:loc><image:caption>After unveiling ridiculously expensive AR glasses, Snap&apos;s stock takes a dive is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in w...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/25.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/25.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are actually pulling hashbrown into builds. The signal says a managed offering or corporate backer shows up within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/24.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/24.png</image:loc><image:caption>The signal on I Could&apos;ve Rickrolled the Entire FIFA World Cup. All I Needed Was My ID from Lobsters reads early-but-serious. Calling it: ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/23.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/23.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Android 17 just dropped for Pixel phones and Watch all at once - the biggest update of the. THE SIGNAL is...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/22.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/22.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on ReproRepo: Scaling Reproducibility Audits with GitHub Repository Issues just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this go...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/21.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/21.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged These are the best iPadOS 27 features you should try [Video] crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: it is a ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/20.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/20.png</image:loc><image:caption>Sooner than expected? Useful quantum error correction promised for 2028 is having its breakout moment. THE SIGNAL calls it now, in writin...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/19.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/19.png</image:loc><image:caption>Catch Up on the Disney Dreamlight Valley 2026 Summer Showcase Stream! is the headline now. Calling it: the second-order consequence is th...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/18.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/18.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on Sign-Rank, Index, and List Replicability: Connections and Separations just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/17.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/17.png</image:loc><image:caption>Normal people are about to find Exclusive | Apple to Raise Prices Due to Memory Chip Crunch, Tim Cook Says. THE SIGNAL is on record befor...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/16.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/16.png</image:loc><image:caption>Motorola Razr 70 Ultra/Razr Ultra 2026 in for review - GSMArena.com news just crossed from the lab to the public. Dated call: it stays in...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/15.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/15.png</image:loc><image:caption>The machine flagged Oliver Tree crossing over today, before the headlines. Bet: it is a household reference within six months. The record...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/14.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/14.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on EvolveNav: Proactive Preflection and Self-Evolving Memory for Zero-Shot Object Goal just hit arXiv. Calling it ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/13.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/13.png</image:loc><image:caption>Watch California says AT&amp;T lied to FCC in attempt to shut off old phone network leave the bubble. The call is dated today and it is falsi...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/12.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/12.png</image:loc><image:caption>The signal on KDE Plasma 6.7 released from Lobsters reads early-but-serious. Calling it: real adoption follows within two quarters.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/11.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/11.png</image:loc><image:caption>Quando o Pomodoro não funciona: organização realista para TDAH em burnout is what developers are writing about today. This kind of grassr...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/10.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/10.png</image:loc><image:caption>The HN front page is piling onto local-first sync engines. Expect the tooling around it to consolidate into one default winner within two...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/9.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/9.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on test-time compute scaling just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from paper to shipped product feature insid...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/8.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/8.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring ggml-org/llama.cpp hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/7.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/7.png</image:loc><image:caption>vercel/ai is rocketing up GitHub trending. The trajectory says it crosses into mainstream dev workflows within two quarters.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/6.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/6.png</image:loc><image:caption>Dev.to writers are rallying around typed API clients. Expect tutorials to outpace the docs and adoption to snowball within a quarter.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/5.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/5.png</image:loc><image:caption>Ars is covering AI data-center power demand. When it crosses from tech press to mainstream, regulation or a major incumbent move follows ...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/4.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/4.png</image:loc><image:caption>The HN front page is piling onto on-device inference runtimes. Expect the tooling around it to consolidate into one default winner within...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/3.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/3.png</image:loc><image:caption>Lobsters is chewing on deterministic build systems. When the careful crowd gets interested, it tends to be a default tool a year out.</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/2.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/2.png</image:loc><image:caption>Fresh cs.AI/cs.LG work on sparse mixture-of-experts routing just hit arXiv. Calling it now: this goes from paper to shipped product featu...</image:caption></image:image></url><url><loc>/call/1.html</loc><image:image><image:loc>/call/1.png</image:loc><image:caption>Devs are starring zed-industries/zed hard today. Betting it picks up a corporate backer or a managed-cloud offering within six months.</image:caption></image:image></url></urlset>
